<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:locale="fil_PH">
    <string name="policy_text" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
        <![CDATA[
            <p><b>Insured</b></p>
            <ul>
                <li>CLIENTS OF ALLIED WORLD HEALTHCARE / REACH52
                (subject to submission of names and or employee number, birth dates, position,
                beneficiary including relationship to the insured in MSExcel format)</li>
            </ul>

            <p><b>Age Eligibility</b></p>
            <ul>
                <li>Not less than eighteen (18) years old nor more than sixty-five (65) years of age</li>
            </ul>

            <p><b>Coverage Period</b></p>
            <ul>
                <li>One (1) year effective on the date to be advised</li>
            </ul>

            <p><b>Conditions/Extensions</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>Accidental Food Poisoning (presence of deleterious matter on food and drinks and not as a result of spoilage/expiration</li>
                <li>Accidental Gas Poisoning</li>
                <li>Acts of Nature</li>
                <li>Amateur and Social Sports</li>
                <li>Animal Bites including mosquito bites (except viral infections/disease following animal/mosquito bites</li>
                <li>Commercial flying as fare paying passenger</li>
                <li>Drowning</li>
                <li>Motorcycling cover including pillion riding excluding whilst engaged in any form of racing, riding exhibition, motocross racing, etc.</li>
                <li>Pyogenic infections acquired through accidental cut or wound</li>
                <li>Riot and strikes (not as an active participant)</li>
                <li>Sabotage and Terrorism (not as an active participant)</li>
                <li>24/7 worldwide coverage; on and off the job</li>
            </ol>

            <p><b>Exclusions</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>loss caused directly or indirectly, wholly or partly by:</li>
                </br><ol type="1">
                    <li>Bacterial infections, viral infections, sickness or disease (except pyogenic infections which shall occur through an accidental cut or wound)</li>
                    <li>Medical or surgical treatment (except such as may be necessary solely by reason of injuries covered by this policy)</li>
                    <li>Miscarriage or pregnancy, any disease of the female reproductive organ</li>
                </ol>
                <li>Suicide or any attempt thereat</li>
                <li>
                    Loss occasioned by war, invasion, act of foreign enemy, hostilities or warlike operations
                    (whether war be declared or not), mutiny, strikes, riots, civil commotion, civil war, rebellion, revolution, insurrection, conspiracy,
                    terrorism, military or usurped power, martial law or state of siege, seizure, quarantine, or customs regulations or naturalization by
                    or under the order of any government or public or local authority. the exclusion shall be affected by any endorsement which does not
                    specifically refer to it, in whole or in part. The application of the exclusion referring to martial law or state of siege is hereby waived
                    for any territorial jurisdiction of the Republic of the Philippines.
                </li>
                <li>Nuclear radiation or radioactive contamination</li>
                <li>Injury sustained while participating in professional athletics, local sports</li>
                <li>
                    Injury sustained while engaging in but not limited to mountaineering
                    requiring the use of ropes or guides, skin diving employing the use of
                    compressed cylinders, racing on wheels or horseback, skydiving from device
                    for aerial navigation, hang gliding or any type of water sports.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Cave-in of mines
                </li>
                <li>
                    Loss of life or injury sustained as a direct result of, in connection with or
                    attributable to the insured being under the influence of prohibited/regulated drugs or alcohol.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Loss of life or injury sustained as a direct result of, in connection with or attributable to;
                    <ol type="1">
                        <li>A commission of a crime or any attempt thereat</li>
                        <li>Violation of rules and regulation on traffic and/or road use</li>
                        <li>Avoiding arrest or</li>
                        <li>Any unlawful act(civil or criminal)</li>
                    </ol>
                </li>
                <li>
                    Coverage on murder and unprovoked is excluded in the following areas:
                    <ol type="1">
                        <li>Autonomous Region of Muslim Mindanao(Basilan, Lanao del Sur, Maguindanao, Sulu Archipelago and Tawi-Tawi</li>
                        <li>Lanao Del Norte</li>
                        <li>North Cotabato</li>
                        <li>South Cotabato</li>
                        <li>Sultan Kudarat</li>
                        <li>Zamboanga Del Norte</li>
                        <li>Zamboanga Del Sur</li>
                        <li>Zamboanga Sibugay</li>
                    </ol>
                </li>
            </ol>

            <p><b>Exclusions Specific to Daily Hospital Income Benefit and Medical Reimbursement cover</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>Pregnancy resulting childbirth. miscarriage or diseases of the female reproductive system</li>
                <li>
                    Routine physical or any other examinations where there are no objective
                    indications or impairment in normal health and laboratory diagnostic of
                    X-ray examinations except in the course of a disability established by the
                    prior call or attendance of a physician.
                </li>
                <li>Intentionally self-inflicted injury or suicide whether sane or insane, or any attempt thereat:</li>
                <li>Cosmetic or plastic surgery, any dental work, dental treatment, eye examination, except as a result of accident</li>
                <li>Any mental and nervous disorder or rest cures</li>
                <li>Treatment of drug addiction or alcoholism</li>
                <li>
                    Sickness or disease occasioned by war, war-like operations, civil
                    commotion, strike, civil war, revolution, rebellion, sabotage, terrorism,
                     service in the armed forces
                </li>
                <li>
                    Sickness or disease as a direct result of, in connection with, or arising from radiation and nuclear activity
                </li>
                <li>
                    Congenital anomalies
                </li>
                <li>
                    Treatment or surgery for tonsils, adenoid, hernia
                </li>
                <li>
                    Venereal Diseases
                </li>
                <li>
                    Murder and Provoked assault
                </li>
                <li>
                    Pre-existing conditions
                </li>
                <li>Acquired Immunology Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS)</li>
                <li>Pneumonia except High Risk Pneumonia and Hospital Acquired Pneumonia (HAP) or Nosocomial Pneumonia</li>
                <li>
                    Dengue, Malaria, Japanese Encephalitis, Hepatitis A, B, C, D and E,
                    Meningococcemia, Cholera, Influenza, Typhoid Fever, Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS)
                    , and Middle East Respiratory Syndrome Corona virus (MERS-Cov)
                </li>
                <li>
                    Widespread diseases, virus outbreak, epidemic or pandemic as declared by the Department of Health
                </li>
            </ol>

            <p><b>Guideline</b></p>
            <ol type="1">
                <li>Master policy shall be issued to Allied World Healthcare / REACH52</li>
                <li>
                    Daily Hospital Income Benefit shall be subject to 5 days exclusion period
                     starting from the effective date of coverage.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Client can avail a maximum of 5 units at any given period of coverage
                </li>
            </ol>
            <p><b>Claim Requirements</b></p>
            <p><b>BASIC REQUIREMENTS</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>Claim Form</li>
                <li>Valid ID</li>
                <li>Other necessary documents that Malayan Insurance may require</li>
            </ol>
            <p><b>ACCIDENTAL DEATH</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>Claim Form</li>
                <li>Valid ID</li>
                <li>Other necessary documents that Malayan Insurance may require</li>
            </ol>
            <p><b>DAILY HOSPITAL INCOME BENEFIT (DHIB)</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>Statement of account issued by the Hospital showing dates of confinement or Date of emergency room treatment</li>
                <li>Medical Certificate from attending physician</li>
            </ol>
            <p><b>MEDICAL REIMBURSEMENT</b></p>
            <ol type="a">
                <li>Photocopy of Official Receipts of the actual medical expenses</li>
                <li>Medical Certificate from attending physician</li>
            </ol>
            <p><b>Territorial Limit</b></p>
            <ul>
                <li>Confinement in a hospital anywhere in the Philippines</li>
            </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>